

# Stephen Muli Kilonzo

Date of birth: 10/07/1992

Nationality: Kenyan

Gender: Male

### **CONTACT**

Moscow, Zelenograd Yunosti 11,

124482 Moscow, Russia

stephenkilonzo.scholar@gmai l.com

(+7) 9779592181

Other: +797779592181



### **ABOUT ME**

I am a kenyan citizen living in Russia. I am a fullstack developer with experience working as a frontend developer (React/Vuejs) and as a backend developer (NodeJs/Python). I hold a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and A Masters in Software Engineering.

### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Node js (express framework) / HTML5/CSS, Javascript / RESTful api / Web Development / Github / SQL / JSON / Object-Oriented Programming / Bootstrap / Git / MySQL / HTML / CSS / Postman / Agile (Scrum) / JavaScript / Unit Testing / REST / Javascript ES6 / Typescript / mongodb

## PARTICIPATION IN PROFESSIONAL COMMUNITIES

### 10/12/2016 - CURRENT

# Participation in professional communities

Github

@ Steve-conqueror1: 188 contributions to 34 repositories, language

|avaScript • HTML • Java • Python • CSS • C #

Bitbucket

https://github.com/Steve-conqueror1

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **14/12/2020 - CURRENT** - Moscow, Khimki

# Fullstack Developer

АЙБИМ

Frontend Developer (React Typescript) - main Backend Developer (Python Pyramid framework)

### **05/11/2019 - 05/12/2020** - Moscow, Russia

# Fullstack Developer

Freelance Developer

Fullstack Developer (NodeJs +VueJs)

### 07/03/2018 - 09/2019 - Tver, Russia

#### Software Intern

Accenture

- JavaScript (react)
- Java (Spring boot)
- $\circ$  SQL

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

**01/09/2019 – 09/06/2021** – Address Id. 1, Shokin Square, Zelenograd, Moscow, Russia, 124498, Zelenograd, Moscow, Russia

# MS Science in Software Engineering

National Research University of Electronic Technology (MIET)

https://eng.miet.ru/

**01/09/2015 – 08/06/2019** – Russia, Tver Komsomolskiy avenue, h.5, Tver

# BSC. Computer Science and Engineering

Tver State Technical University

https://tstu.tver.ru/